Coordonnées

+25777567042 (Mobile) victoiremmanuelbarh@gmail.c om

www.linkedin.com/in/victor-barh (LinkedIn) github.com/vic778 (Other)

Principales compétences

English Ruby on Rails React.js

Certifications

Programming in HTML with JavaScript and CSS nodejs

Publications BECOMING A WEB DEVELOPER

Victoir Barherenduba

Full-Stack Developer | Ruby | Ruby on Rails | Javascript | React | Redux

Ntunja Township

Résumé

Full-Stack JavaScript Developer | Entrepreneur | Founder

Versatile JavaScript developer with hands-on experience in developing and building technology startups (B2B and customercentric) by bringing together a vision, strategy, and execution in a totally unstructured and resource-constrained environment.

During my 2 years of experience in the technology field, I have gained extensive knowledge in

- Front-end development: ReactJS |JQuery
- Back-end development: NodeJS | ExpressJS | Ruby on Rails
- Databases : Postgres | MongoDB
- Stylization: SASS | CSS-in-JS | MaterialUI | Bootstrap
- -Site deployment: Heroku | Netlify | Github

Passionate about ideating, conceptualizing, and producing consumer-centric technology and technology products. I'm open to exploring exciting full development opportunities in startups or large-scale companies.

Take a look at some of my work at https://github.com/vic778.

Looking for a developer? Let's schedule a Zoom chat! Send me an e-mail at barhvictor@gmail.com.

Expérience

Microverse Code reviwer mars 2022 - Present (1 mois)

Acklen Avenue Frontend Developer septembre 2021 - mars 2022 (7 mois)

- * Task sharing while using the Kanban method of Github in the repository project.
- * Update old applications while using the new React Update.

JUUBIX

Back End Developer

mars 2021 - juillet 2021 (5 mois)

creation of websites from scratch while following the division of tasks within the group.

how to work in a team while being at a distance. how to collaborate with your teammates.

Microverse

Developer

décembre 2020 - décembre 2020 (1 mois)

Manzini, Eswatini

Mentored junior web developers, providing technical support through code reviews.

Proposed improvements to code organization to improve code quality and overall performance.

Provided advice and tips on how to maintain motivation to maintain longevity in the program.

Banro Corp

IT Support Specialist

avril 2018 - juillet 2020 (2 ans 4 mois)

Kinshasa, Kinshasa, Congo (DRC)

- * Handling the overall network.
- * Supported local users.
- * Provided support to the software of digital knitwear machines to convert its menu to Kinshasa.

Formation

Microverse

· (octobre 2021)

Hope Africa University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (janvier 2016 - décembre 2019)